export const QuestionData = [
  {
    question: "What is the primary function of a Database Management System (DBMS)?",
    options: ["To manage computer networks", "To manage computer hardware", "To manage data storage and retrieval", "To manage software applications"],
    answer: 3
  },
  {
    question: "What is the term for a program or software that performs a specific task?",
    options: ["Algorithm", "Application", "System", "Utility"],
    answer: 2
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of the model that describes how data is processed and stored in a computer system?",
    options: ["Input-Process-Output (IPO) model", "Data-Information-Knowledge (DIK) model", "System Development Life Cycle (SDLC) model", "Hardware-Software-Network (HSN) model"],
    answer: 1
  },
  {
    question: "What is the term for a network that connects devices in a limited geographical area, such as a home or office building?",
    options: ["Wide Area Network (WAN)", "Local Area Network (LAN)", " Metropolitan Area Network (MAN)", "Wireless Network (WN)"],
    answer: 2
  },
  {
    question: "What is the process of converting data into a code that can only be deciphered with a key or password?",
    options: ["Encryption", "Decryption", "Compression", "Decompression"],
    answer: 1
  },
  {
    question: "What is the term for a software development methodology that emphasizes iterative and incremental development?",
    options: ["Agile", "Waterfall", "Scrum", "Kanban"],
    answer: 1
  },
  {
    question: "What is the term for a computer system that can perform tasks automatically without human intervention?",
    options: ["Autonomous system", "Artificial intelligence system", "Machine learning system", "Robotics system"],
    answer: 1
  },
  {
    question: "What is the term for a type of software that manages and coordinates the activities of a business?",
    options: ["Enterprise Resource Planning (ERP) system", "Customer Relationship Management (CRM) system", "Supply Chain Management (SCM) system", "Human Resource Management (HRM) system"],
    answer: 1
  },
  {
    question: "What is the term for a type of network attack in which an attacker sends a large amount of traffic to a network in an attempt to overwhelm it?",
    options: ["Phishing", "Malware", "Denial of Service (DoS)", "Ransomware"],
    answer: 3
  },
  {
    question: "What is the term for a type of software that allows users to create, edit, and manage digital content?",
    options: ["Content Management System (CMS)", "Document Management System (DMS)", "Record Management System (RMS)", "Digital Asset Management System (DAMS)"],
    answer: 1
  }
];